<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.adventium.design.exploration.feature"
      label="Design Space Explorer"
      version="1.0.1.qualifier"
      provider-name="Adventium Enterprises, LLC">

   <description url="http://www.example.com/description">
      Design Space Explorer (DSE) generates instance models from declarative models.
OSATE does this too, but requires implementations all the way down.

AADL allows subcomponents to be types, that may have several implementations.
However, AADL will not generate an instance model needed for many analysis tools,
and especially, verification condition generation by the BLESS Proof Tool.

DSE provides a checkbox tree so a user can select which implementations are 
desired when subcomponents are types.

These configurations can be saved and recalled so the user doesn&apos;t need to check 
boxes every time DSE is used.

In addition, when a property set contains *only* property constants having
aadlinteger type, DSE will allow you to change them.  This was included 
especially for component and port array sizes to allow different parts of the 
system to have different levels of redundancy for fault tolerance tradeoff
analysis.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.example.com/copyright">
      --------------------------------------------------------------------------
Copyright 2021 Adventium Enterprises, LLC

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the &quot;License&quot;);
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

    http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.example.com/license">
      --------------------------------------------------------------------------
Copyright 2021 Adventium Enterprises, LLC

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the &quot;License&quot;);
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

    http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------
   </license>

   <plugin
         id="com.adventium.design.exploration"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
